Don't worry, everyone!
The Special Assault Team will
be providing support now!
Stay calm and follow the orders you're given!
The Tokyo Float...
We're really abandoning Japan, aren't we?
What's wrong? Are you scared?
What about you?
Aren't you scared?
Not at all.
I'll beat all the bad guys for you!
Really?
Yup!
Don't worry.
I'll protect everyone!
Episode 5
Beauty of the Land of Rubble -Batlantis-
Baths
I never thought this day would come!
There's a huge bath in this building,
but I can't use it since it's the girls' dorm.
Then I'll let you have it
all to yourself tonight.
Go have fun.
Thanks, Sis!
Let's get bathing!
L-Listen, Himekawa!
Wh-What are you doing?
Lecher! Pervert!
Peeping Tom! Eros Overlord!
N-No! It's a misunderstanding!
Hear me out!
No excuses!
Neros!
L-Lewd.
When I gave you sole access to the baths?
Of course, I didn't tell Himekawa.
Your relationship isn't developing at all,
so I prepared a bit of an event.
I'm disappointed with the result, though.
So it was your fault!
I'm disappointed in you, Commander!
I can't believe you'd do something like this!
Then let me ask you something:
how much of your Hybrid Count is left?
How much has it recovered
since the last battle?
W-Well...
Yurishia and Aine have already succeeded
in performing a Heart Hybrid.
You're the only one who hasn't.
Heart Hybrid?
Why would I do something so indecent?
And with Hida-kun, no less!
A map of the world doesn't really
do much good these days.
All the world's megafloats have had their
communications cut off from one another.
We don't know where they are.
Megafloat Japan is... Hmm...
If we were going to run into anybody,
it would be West USA,
maybe.
It's true that I haven't really done a
Heart Hybrid with Himekawa yet.
I don't really get it, either.
I need to fix that.
And...
I won't let any of them die.
Call me a pervert if you want.
I'll...
Kizuna!
Sis?
Come to Industrial Area 18, warehouse 4.
There's something I want to show you.
What's this?
The simulator we'd been
working on is finally complete.
It's capable of recreating any situation.
This is the simulator's scenario function.
It can also change clothes.
Wow! This'll make it easy to have
mock battles with Magitech weapons!
It's perfect for a guy like me to train.
It can also recreate any kind of date spot,
hotel, or anything else one might prefer.
It can also create accessories,
toys, and tools.
It has a bed, a shower, a jacuzzi,
and even a karaoke machine.
A bed?
Is this...?
Of course.
It's a dating simulator...
...that we developed to make
things with the girls smoother.
We call it the Love Room.
By the way, the Engineering Division put
their full efforts into this project.
Say thanks to our young talents!
Hooray! Hooray!
Even if it's to help the Eros Overlord,
as long as we can be of
use to Director Shikina...
I, Momo Kurumizawa,
will do whatever it takes!
That's not what advanced technology is for!
Incorrect!
Deepening the bonds of trust between you
and creating mental and physical
pleasure and excitement...
If you want to get the maximum
out of your Hybrid Hearts,
that's indispensable.
How can you say that with a
serious look on your face?
So this is what you like, huh?
No, I—!
In any event,
I order you to use this facility to
perform a Heart Hybrid immediately.
I need you to find out how effective it is.
So what did you want me to do?
Try and patch things up with Hayuru for you?
Um...
I wanted your help testing a new simulator.
Wow!
This is amazing!
What kind of situation would excite Yurishia?
I can't exactly ask her.
Something wrong, Yurishia?
N-Nothing.
What's with this room?
It's low-class. And perverted.
Can you switch it back
to the other hotel room?
S-Sure...
Maybe...
Wh-What is this?
S-Sorry.
Looks like the system's screwing up.
The system's screwing up?
Jeez...
Does he like seeing me this way?
When I think of Kizuna looking at me,
it turns me on.
Then maybe my system will screw up, too.
I'll do better things to you
than Hayuru ever would.
Wh-What?
K-Kizuna?!
What are you doing?
Take these off!
Was this the pleasure and
excitement Sis was talking about?
Then...
K-Kizuna?!
Where are you touching me?
No!
Yurishia...
Can I take off your top?
I'm going to take it off.
What is this?
This is...
Yurishia...
Kizuna?
Are we done?
Don't worry.
The Heart Hybrid...
...was a success.
Come on, go out with me.
Huh? I don't know...
What are you doing?
The school is a sacred place.
Crap, it's the disciplinary committee!
What am I doing?
Himekawa!
Listen, Himekawa.
Will you go out with me for a little?
Go out with you?
I can't just ask her...
...to Hybrid Heart all of a sudden, can I?
Um, I...
Captain!
Sylvia?
What is it?
Look!
The results of my last test!
Wow!
All A's!
I got the best in the class!
I worked really hard so you would praise me!
I see.
Good girl.
Sorry, but I have somewhere to be.
Himekawa?
What was I expecting?
I'm such a fool.
I don't...
...have the right!
Mysterious radio waves?
Yes. Last night, at 2:10
Megafloat Japan Standard Time,
we detected a weak radio signal.
Its source was...
Guam.
Guam?
We know nothing about
the origin of the signal.
But there is a US military base on Guam,
and there's a good chance that
someone sent it from there.
Which means there might be a survivor?
A survivor?
Friend or enemy,
someone sent us a message from there.
Our mission this time...
...is to determine the source
of the radio waves.
You will make land at Guam.
Make land?
But there's an Entrance there, right?
It's too dangerous!
Don't worry.
I'll wipe out the enemy with
my Immoral Weapon if I have to.
Oh? I thought you couldn't
use the Pulverizer anymore.
It disappeared after a while, right?
That Immoral Weapon you're so proud of.
Th-Then I can just do a Climax Hybrid again.
No way! It's my turn to try!
Say, Kizuna.
How about we pick up where we left off?
Enough!
What did you think?
Those radio waves seemed to be
sending some kind of data.
We won't know what we'll find until we
get there, but if we're going to look,
we may as well go all the way.
And if the sender is Dr. Nayuta?
Then I'll handle it myself.
So this is Guam.
It's quiet.
Let's split up.
Himekawa and I will check the city of Tumon.
Yurishia and Aine, you two
check out Anderson Air Base.
Roger!
Looks like they cleaned the place out
before they left.
A shining example for soldiers everywhere.
Yup.
Except for this.
This is terrible.
Damn it.
Himekawa?
It's nothing.
I see.
If there's a survivor, this time I'll...
Thanks, miss.
Are you a survivor?
Don't worry.
It's okay now!
We're with Amaterasu, from Megafloat Japan.
My, my.
It's just like she said...
If I come here, I might see them.
You're not who I've been waiting for,
but that's okay.
You'll have to do.
Zeeru!
Is that a Heart Hybrid Gear?
So that's what you call
the Magitech armor, huh?
What country are you with?
Where did you get that Gear?
Country?
What other country could I be from?
The proud Empire of Batlantis!
Batlantis?
You don't know it?
That's a shame.
It rules more than half the planet.
Of course, I'm talking about the world
on the other side of that.
An Entrance?
N-No way!
You're not...
My name is Aldea.
From your perspective,
I'm from another dimension.
So, anyway...
I'm going to...
...take your cores out, okay?
What is she?
Is she really from another dimension?
That's boring.
You just started running?
Let's have some more fun.
I don't really know what's going on,
but it's clear she's our enemy.
Then...
Sword!
Blades!
What?
We saw this before!
Is that all you've got?
Entertain me more!
Hida-kun!
Why, you!
This is so boring.
Let's finish it.
What's that?
I wondered what all the fuss was.
Yurishia!
You've got guts,
having a clandestine meeting
with a strange girl.
Aine...
I want more information, but it's okay.
I'll catch her and make her tell me.
A white Magitech armor.
We finally meet.
Are you the one who sent that signal?
What are you talking about?
Anyway, you're the one who fired
that huge cannon before, aren't you?
What if I am?
Who is she?
Hey, can I ask you a question?
Are you—?
You bitch!
Get out of my way!
Oh dear.
Now I've done it.
Sheesh!
What a pain.
What?
I'm bored, so I'm going to finish this quick.
I can take the cores off your bodies.
So relax and die.
What is that?
A-A bomb?
This is...
Himekawa!
Blades!
Himekawa's blades aren't working?
Take this! Take this! Take this!
Take this! Take this!
Himekawa!
Its armor is so thick!
Move, Aine!
Fire!
No way...
What do we do, Kizuna?
At this rate...
We've got no choice but to retreat.
Himekawa?
That Magitech weapon...
I'll destroy her, no matter what!
We're retreating, Himekawa.
That's an order.
Roger.
Oh, did you think you could escape?
My magic really does run out fast in Lemuria.
But...
This is going to be fun.
What is that thing?
Hey, Kizuna?
What's going on?
The Batlantis Empire?
People from another dimension?
And I've never seen that
Magitech weapon before.
Eros You Next Week!
Creator: Kazuya Morimae
The day Tokyo burned,
I decided that I would never forgive myself.
That was my punishment.
But when I met him...
Next time:
World-Splitter -Gladius-
What is this feeling?